[SUBARU] Is there
really not a single person,
even if anyone is--
just the slightest
memory of him.
Enough, Subaru.
It's fine.
He should know
that this is Julius.
Julius Juukulius in full.
I think you've all
figured this out,
but he's one
of Gluttony's victims
that's been left nameless.
That said, his mind
is still intact.
He's not like Gluttony's
other victims.
They all either had their
memories consumed and ended up
like Lady Crusch,
or had both their names
and their memories consumed
and ended up in a state
like Rem's But with Julius,
only his name was consumed.
So you mean
he's an exception?
Everybody else
has forgotten, but
he still remembers who he is?
Your uniform tells me
that you must be a knight.
I'm sure you must have
been an acquaintance
of myself and Felix.
Perhaps even we were
closer than that.
At the very least.
I thought of both of you
as important friends of mine.
Damn it.
[ANASTASIA] You think you
were just everyday friends?
If you ask me, I think there's
a lot more to it than that.
Lady Anastasia.
[sighs]
I've got a suggestion I'd
like to share with all of you.
May I?
In these city walls,
there are many people
who were either
transformed by Lust,
or who were left without their
names, thanks to Gluttony.
We may have captured
the Sin Archbishops and all,
but I doubt they're
going to just come
out and give us
the secret to fixing
everything just like that.
We're in a bit of a pickle.
You thought now was
the appropriate time
to bring that up?
And that means we've just
got to ask someone else who
has the knowledge to tell us.
Someone we can tell
everything, who's really smart?
That's right.
And you see, there's someone
who's "really smart" here
in this city, ain't there?
Quit being vague
and just spit it out then.
You mean?
Shaula the sage.
Shaula?
Yep.
Of the Three Great
Heroes of Lugunica.
[NARRATOR] Shaula the sage.
[SUBARU] Long ago,
in the Dragon Friend Kingdom
of Lugunica, there was
an accomplished band of heroes.
They were the Master Swordsman,
the Dragon Lord and the Sage,
together known
as the Three Great Heroes.
That right?
Yep.
The keeper of knowledge who
foresees all that will ever be,
standing at the far
eastern edge of Lugunica,
in the Auguria
dunes, we'll find
the Pleiades Watchtower,
which was built to guard
the sealed Witch of Envy.
The legendary sage lives
there in total seclusion.
And if my hunch is right,
she might just have
the answers we're looking for.
[OTTO] To be frank,
I'm still against going
through with this plan.
I mean, aren't we
talking about a place
even you weren't
able to reach before?
Two years back, when illness
befell the royal family,
the council sent me
out on special orders,
hoping I could find a cure.
My goal was
the Pleiades Watchtower.
But I never made it there,
no matter how far I traveled.
The tower in the distance
never drew closer.
It must have been
some sort of barrier,
and I found myself
unable to cross it.
The Auguria dunes
are famous for being
a giant den of mabests,
if I recall correctly.
Should Mr. Natsuki
and the others really
be going to a dangerous
place like that on their own?
[REINHARD] We must have faith.
I have a duty to fulfill,
escorting Lady Felt
and that Sin Archbishop.
Besides, it's
painfully obvious,
this city's people
still need us.
[chuckles]
[fire crackling]
[SUBARU] A place that
even Reinhardt has tried
and failed to get into, huh?
Just hearing that part
alone makes all this
seem pretty dang hopeless.
[BEATRICE]
Subaru, you're getting
a scary look on your face.
If your worries cause you to
neglect our physical contact,
then you see, old Betty's
cuteness will go to waste,
I suppose.
I'm sorry.
Wait, you're right.
I only zoned out
for a minute there,
and now you're such an uggo.
That is a dirty lie.
[laughing]
[EMILIA] Beatrice.
Huh?
Isn't it just
about your bedtime?
Would you like
to come sleep with me?
[yawns]
I will, I suppose.
Staying up all night is bad
for your health, after all.
[owl hooting]
[ANASTASIA] Natsuki,
you're still up?
Yeah.
Even on a safe road,
it's best for someone
to keep watch, right?
Right, we just don't have
enough people, do we?
I sure wish Ricardo
would have been
able to come with
us on this journey.
But with his arm like that.
[SUBARU] How about you
tell me the truth already?
Huh?
Where's this coming from?
What are you talking about?
You're a seriously
lousy actor.
Just drop it.
[sighs]
I know you're not
Lady Anastasia.
That face and voice aren't your
playthings, so knock it off.
How interesting.
How did you figure out that
I wasn't the actual Ana?
Something has seemed off
with you this whole time,
but now I know for certain.
It's true that lady
Anastasia is a realist,
but there's no way she'd
ever talk so coldly
about a close friend
dealing with such
a life changing injury.
[sighs]
I keep getting outed
like this left and right.
It's kind of embarrassing.
Wait, hold on.
You mean I'm not the only one?
Priscilla Barrielle,
the one who called me a vixen?
She sure is a scary woman.
Who exactly are you, then?
And what are you trying to do?
Echidna.
What?
My name is Echidna.
And what I am is
an artificial spirit.
Frankly, it's not all that
surprising that you'd assume I
took possession of Ana's body.
That's why I was hesitant
to tell you the truth.
What kind of terrible
joke is this?
So you're Echidna?
Is Lady Anastasia--
[gasps]
You don't mean, all the
terrible things that happened
in Priestella were your doing?
Would you just
calm down a sec?
I think there's a huge
misunderstanding here.
You expect me to calm down
after all that, you vile witch?
What the hell have you
done with Lady Anastasia?
Please, I wish
you'd stop treating
me like some evil mastermind.
I promise, I have no
intention of harming her.
Besides, I've been together
with her for over 10 years.
What the hell are you--
wait, over 10 years?
Mm-hmm.
First of all, let me clear
up the misunderstanding.
The Echidna that
you're thinking of
is someone completely
different from me.
The thing is,
other than the fact
that I was created
as an artificial spirit,
and the fact that my name is
Echidna, I know next to nothing
about myself.
You're an artificial
spirit, same as Beako?
Strictly speaking,
this fox muffler
Ana's always wearing around her
neck is actually my real body.
So you see, I've been watching
all of you for a long time.
Why would you choose
now for this reveal?
Is it because you're finally
prepared to take full control
over her body, Foxidna?
Foxidna?
I can't say that I'm
particularly fond of that name.
I had no intention
of taking over Ana's body.
This unfortunate outcome
isn't what I had hoped for.
If that's the truth
and it's not what you wanted,
why not go back
into that fox muffler?
Believe me, I would
love to do just that.
But that's no longer an option.
And why is that?
What's wrong with
Lady Anastasia's body
that you can't leave?
I'm going to be blunt.
I'm using Ana's Od as a medium
to overwrite her mind
with my own consciousness.
Her consciousness is sleeping
in the depths of her Od,
giving me complete
control over her body.
I can even cast magic
by using her gate,
even though it's
rather defective.
Wait, something's
wrong with her gate?
Then if you're using
magic that consistently,
wouldn't it put way too
much strain on her body?
The only reason I'd
ever risk her life
is because it was already
in danger to begin with.
I have, of course, talked
with Ana about this
and earned her consent.
So this isn't the first time?
You've borrowed
her body before?
There were a few other
occasions, but none
where I was unable to return.
So I'm at a loss as to what
to do right now myself.
[fire crackling]
The thing is, I love Ana.
I don't know if I'm
right about this
since I've never
had one myself,
but I feel as if she's
something very close to what
people call family.
All I want is for her to be
as healthy, and above all,
as happy as possible.
So your real reason
for wanting to go
see the sage is actually--
Mm.
My one goal is to
figure out a way I can
give Ana's body back to her.
To do that, I won't hesitate
to use you and your companions.
I understand what you want
and all, but are you sure
the sage knows how to get
you back to normal?
No, I'm not.
However, if the sage
is powerful,
if she really sees
all and knows all,
like the stories say,
there's a chance.
I will make the choice that
offers the highest probability
of success, period.
[sighs]
That's kind of a lot
you just sprung on me.
But I at least understand.
You have a clear goal,
as well as a solid plan
of action to accomplish it.
It's not something that'll
get in the way of what
we're trying to do either.
Indeed.
At the end of the day,
we're both going because
we have questions for the sage.
Right then.
All I ask is not to mention
borrowing Lady Anastasia's body
to Julius, OK?
In fact, don't
tell anyone at all.
I don't have
a problem with that.
But I'm surprised you
wouldn't want to tell them.
Only because the timing
sucks as it is,
and I really don't want
to make any unnecessary waves
right now.
Makes sense.
After all, you have
something else you want
to ask the sage to help with.
Something more personal, right?
[SUBARU] Well, that's--
So then, we'll make a stop
at Margrave Mather's mansion
on the way.
I'm sure you want
to prepare yourself
to cross the dunes
soon, but the mansion
is where that sleeping
beauty of yours is.
You do intend to take
her with you, correct?
If you ask me, that's not
such a bad idea, you know.
We'll still save all of them.
It just comes down
to who's going to be
the first one in line, really.
I don't think
anyone would blame
you if you used your position
to make that her.
[SUBARU] Rem.
[MARGRAVE] Your letter
informed me of the situation.
You managed minimal
casualties in the battle
against Sin Archbishops.
It brings me
great relief to know
that Garf was of use as well.
Also, I am grateful Master
Otto seems to be all right.
Mr. Otto is always way
too reckless, though.
And after we were able to send
out such fantastic news, too.
Oh right, the meeting
with the fakes.
I heard it was
something to celebrate.
You'll have to fill us in on
all the details later, then.
Yeah.
I mean, yes.
Oh.
Natsuki, what a very
sinful man you are.
Right.
Now, after that,
it's clear to see
why people have
been calling you
the little girl user, Subaru.
Just so you know, it's
not really fair to call
Petra a little girl now.
And if I do use
any little girls,
it would only be Beako, OK?
Mhm!
The outcome we
had in Priestella
wasn't just thanks
to Garfiel and Otto.
Everyone in the city worked
hard together to achieve it.
But still.
You're heading
for the sage's tower
in order to discover
a way to save the victims
of Gluttony and Lust, right?
A dangerous path indeed.
Is there even
a chance of success?
Margrave Mathers, I
understand your concern.
I know this is of great
importance to you.
However, there are still many
people suffering in Priestella.
Their bodies and minds left
damaged thanks to the witch
cult's nefarious deeds.
Oh my, you put that
so very elegantly.
And since I have
not recognized you,
I assume you are one
of them yourself, correct?
We're talking about
where things stand here.
We made a stop at the mansion
for Rem and one more.
The small girl
who is currently
in the mansion's prison, yes?
[locks clicking]
My, My, I sure didn't
expect to see you here.
Yeah.
I have important business
to talk about with you, Meili.
[MEILI] The Auguria dunes, huh?
I've been there before
to get myself more mabeasts.
You should know that place
is really teeming with them.
That's it.
That's what I want to know.
I want to learn from
the experiences of someone
who's actually been out there.
I mean, there's a huge
difference between info
that comes from someone's
firsthand knowledge and
info that doesn't, you know?
And it's very
reassuring for someone
without any of that at all.
[sighs]
If there's something you want
me to do, just spit it out.
OK.
If we have a mabeast
user like you with us,
we might make it through
the dunes in one piece.
So, would you come
with us, and--
All right.
Yeah, I realize you
don't want to go outside,
and I'm asking a lot, but if
you could maybe just-- uh?
Do I have to repeat myself?
I said I'm willing
to go along with you.
What?
Really?
Sure thing.
I'll take care
of the mabeast problem
in whatever way you want me to.
I can keep them away
from us, tame them,
make them kill each
other, or even make
them eat the sage if you want.
It's your choice.
At the very least, please
don't do those last two.
But I'm confused.
I thought that
you were refusing
to leave the mansion at all.
I'm still afraid of mom
finding me and everything,
but I don't want to be locked
up in here forever, so.
This won't be some
fun little jaunt.
It's my first walk in a while.
I think I could
use a little fun.
OK.
Look forward
to working together.
Don't start getting all
friendly with me, though.
I have no intention
of following in Beatrice and
Petra's footsteps, understand?
Hey, Julius, what's up?
I was just thinking.
About being forgotten,
and forgetting.
Which one is more
painful, I wonder?
Why would you expect
me to have the answer?
Knock it off with
the emo stuff.
Who cares which one is
worse than the other?
Both of them can kiss my ass.
Stop making a competition
over how painful things are.
Subaru.
And quit looking like
a little kicked puppy.
Did you forget
or something, Julius?
No, you can't forget, Julius.
I've seen with my own two
eyes how strong you are.
My shame always reminds me.
It doesn't matter
if no one else knows.
Just, you truly are
a remarkable man, you know?
I'm realizing it
all over again.
But yes, you're right.
It's not as if I've
been left behind
by everything and everyone.
You couldn't be left behind.
If anything, it's more
like you've always
been three lengths ahead.
Don't you think three
is a bit conservative?
Do you want me
to kick your ass?
Beako and I have come a hell of
a long way as a team, you know.
[Julius chuckles]
Hi, Ram.
I was just preparing
for our departure.
I bathed her and dressed her
in fresh clothes.
You're getting a lewd look
on your face, pervert.
I kept quiet because I
didn't know what to say,
and that's what I get?
You really might
die this time.
Why are you doing this?
[SUBARU] I think
I can't help but
want to be the very
first thing she sees
when she finally wakes up.
Taking feelings out
of the equation,
I know it doesn't matter who
does it, just that it happens.
But the thing is, when
emotions come into play,
I want to save her.
I want to give
everything I have
and be the one
to bring her back.
[RAM] You're so dumb.
Sorry it took me
so long to come see you.
There was a bunch of other
stuff I had to take care of.
Sorry, that's just an excuse.
It might really mean
something this time.
I'm going to save
you to get you back.
I swear, that's a promise.
[REALA] After you traveled
all this way, sorry,
I don't have anything
special prepared for you.
Nah, my bad
for dropping by like this.
We really don't want to put
you through any trouble.
Oh, it's not any
trouble at all.
You took the time and effort
to come here and visit me.
If anything, seeing
you puts me at ease.
My husband, Garek, will
be home any time now.
I have total faith in him.
When I was empty inside and had
nothing, he came into my life
and granted me
these past 10 years.
He even gave me an adorable
daughter and son.
See, he's given me
so many wonderful things,
how could I not believe in him?
You are so strong.
[REALA] Yeah, of course I am.
I mean, as a mother of two,
that's to be expected.
Oh, right, there's something
that's been on my mind.
And so I wanted to ask
you, Mr. Gorgeous
Tiger, you always seem to show
so much concern for us.
Can you tell me
why that might be?
Uh, I just can't
take my eyes off you.
It's hard to explain.
And you guys are, well, kind
of losing it, aren't you?
Oh, my, how mean.
But unfortunately, it is true,
so I can't argue with you.
Huh?
Losing what, hair?
I totally get it, cause
I lose a bunch of hair
when it's hot, too.
[laughing]
Are you all right,
Mr. Gorgeous Tiger?
I'm not sure why,
but right now,
you look like
a young child who's
about to burst into tears.
[sobs]
[somber music]
[GARFIEL] Mom.
Mom.
It's just that I really want--
I really want my mom.
He's Garfiel.
That's his real name.
Huh?
[sobbing]
Hey, Garfiel.
Hey, Mom.
I miss you.
Mom.
[sobs]
[REALA] There, there.
Oh, Garf, sweetie, good boy.
All this time, you've been
giving it everything, huh?
[GARFIEL] I have.
I tried so hard.
Gave it all I had.
But I got so many things wrong.
And still, and still everyone--
[REALA] It's all right.
It'll all be OK, Garf.
Your mother is
here with you now.
[sobbing]
[groans]
Hey, Garf, you good?
Yeah.
Gorgeous Tiger, are you OK?
I can't believe I just saw a
boy cry his eyes out like that.
Sorry to go and freak
you all out like that.
It's about time that we
head out, so you can relax.
Please come visit
again anytime you'd like.
When you feel like
crying, I'd be
more than happy to help you
by lending you my shoulder
in your mother's stead.
And I'll do whatever I can to
make sure that doesn't happen.
[REALA] Come on now, you two,
let's say our goodbyes, OK?
Gorgeous Tiger, see you.
Now, Rafiel, you too.
Rafiel?
Yes, that's right.
Oh, did I never actually
properly introduce you to them?
Better late than
never, I suppose.
This is Fred and Rafiel.
I came up with both
of their names myself.
Those names were from you?
Yes.
I was trying to think of some
cute names for babies,
and those ones just came to me.
Fred and Rafiel.
Frederica, Garfiel.
[laughs]
Well, see you later,
Rafiel and Fred.
I'll be back.
OK.
See you soon then.
Hey, next time you come, you
better not be a big crybaby.
Heh.
Thanks, Mom.
I'll drop by for a visit again.
Take care of yourselves
till then.